A Guide to the National Committee on United States-China Relations records, RG 5, Accession 5 FA1187
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Programs, Projects and Proposals, 1962, 1965-1976, 1992-2006; 8
  - Ussuri Project: Adirondack Understandings, 1994 August 11 (Box 13, Folder 124)
    Conclusion of discussions held at Lake Placid, NY, August 11, 1994 (by American, Chinese, and Russian participants in the Land Use Planning delegation visit).
  - Ussuri Project: Trip Reports by Americans, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 125)
  - Ussuri Project: Chinese Specialist Reports, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 126)
    English translations.
  - Ussuri Project: Chinese Specialist Reports (Originals), 1994 (Box 14, Folder 127)
  - Ussuri Project: Russian Papers and Reports, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 128)
  - Ussuri Project: Steering Committee Meeting and Map Exchange, 1995 February 17-24 (Box 14, Folder 129)
    Planning correspondence, 1994-1995.
  - Ussuri Project: Steering Committee Meeting, 1995 February 17-24 (Box 14, Folder 130)
    Agenda, notes, follow-up, and press.
  - Ussuri Project: Harbin Understandings, 1995 February 28 (Box 14, Folder 131)
    Agreements reached at the Steering Committee meeting in Harbin, February 18-24, concerning the Ussuri Project draft report and subsequent meetings.
  - Ussuri Project: Draft Report (No. 3) - Outside Comments, 1995 June - September (Box 14, Folder 132)
    Comments on Draft Ussuri River Watershed and Central Sikhote-Alin Sustainable Land Use and Allocation Program. File includes Trip Report by Thomas Lumpkin and David Hoch (for Ecologically Sustainainable Development, ESD), 1995 June 15-23, Heilongjiang Province, and Trip Report on Visit to Far East Russia, by Bruce Marcot, 1995 July 31 - August 16.
  - Ussuri Project: George Davis, Gordon Davis, Elizabeth Knup Trip, and Hydrology Fieldwork, 1995 June (Box 14, Folder 133)
  - Ussuri Project: Bilateral Field Verification in Russia, 1995 August (Box 14, Folder 134)
  - Ussuri Project: Field Verification in China, 1995 October (Box 14, Folder 135)
  - FA1187:009 - Ussuri Project: Field Verification in China, 1995 October; Still Images: 2 5x7 and 9 3x5 color prints. (Box 63, Folder 135)
    Group photos from trip, including from public meeting in Shuangyashan. George Davis, Elizabeth Knup, and Chinese participants.
  - Ussuri Project: Legislative Working Groups, 1995-1996 (Box 15, Folder 136)
    Draft implementation legislation for sustainable development policies in the Ussuri River basin. File includes the draft regulations, Chinese revisions, and correspondence concerning the process.
  - Ussuri Project: Legislative Working Groups (Draft Legislation), 1995-1996; Floppy disk: 3 1/2 inch. (Box 15, Folder 136)
    Disk contains the revised text of the draft legislation (file USSLAREV.WP5) (and may contain the original English text). Sent by translator Sheree Willis to Elizabeth Knup, November 12, 1995.
  - Ussuri Project: Steering Committee Meeting, 1996 April (Box 15, Folder 137)
    Vladivostok.
  - FA1187:010 - Ussuri Project: Steering Committee Meeting, 1996 April; Still Images: 19 color prints (4x6 and 3x5) (Box 63, Folder 137)
    Meeting, April 4-10, Vladivostok.
  - Ussuri Project: Final Stages, 1996-1997 (Box 15, Folder 138)
  - Ussuri Project: Governors' Meeting (Agenda and Memorandum of Understanding), 1998 May 25-27 (Box 15, Folder 139)
    International Conference on the Ussuri River Watershed Sustainable Development Strategy Initiation. File includes a color photocopy image (4x6) of the Memorandum of Understanding signing.
  - Ussuri Project: Heilongjiang Province Delegation, 2000 September (Box 15, Folder 140)
  - Ussuri Project: Fundraising (General), 1992-1997 (Box 15, Folder 141)
    Approaches to Mars Foundation, Dodge Foundation, Mertz-Gilmore Foundation, Heinz Foundation, AT&T Foundation, W. Alton Jones Foundation.
  - Ussuri Project: Possible Funding and Support - Japan, 1994-1995 (Box 15, Folder 142)
  - Ussuri Project: U. S. Agency for International Development (AID) Grant (Russia), 1994-1995 (Box 15, Folder 143)
  - Ussuri Project: Weeden Foundation Grants, 1993-1998 (Box 15, Folder 144)
  - Ussuri Project: Investment Document and Potential Investors, 1995-1997 (Box 15, Folder 145)
    File includes Executive Summary and Economic Development portions of the Ussuri Sustainable Land Use Program report. Also includes proposal for study of U. S. and Japanese investment strategies in Shanghai and Vladivostok (1995).
  - Ussuri Project: Press Coverage, 1994-1995 (Box 15, Folder 146)
  - Ussuri Project: Press Release and Publicity, 1997 January-August (Box 15, Folder 147)
  - Ussuri Project: Publicity Tour, 1996-1997 (Box 15, Folder 148)
    Plans appear to have been dropped due to funding and other difficulties.
  - Ussuri Project: Add-On Activities, 1995-1996 (Box 16, Folder 149)
    Includes presentations at conferences in Sanjiang, Shenyang, Victoria, BC, and others.
  - Ussuri Project: U. S. State Department Presentation, 1997 September 10 (Box 16, Folder 150)
  - FA1187:019 - Ussuri Project: U. S. State Department Presentation, 1997 September 10; Oversized: Map (approx. 38 x 60"). (Folder Oversized 1)
    Map: Recommended General Land Use Allocations for Sustainable Development of the Ussuri River Watershed and Adjacent Territories (Two-sided: North Sheet and South Sheet). Copyright, 1997. Ecologically Sustainable Development Inc.
  - Ussuri Project: Ecologically Sustainable Development Inc. (ESD) Demise, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 151)
    Original folder labeled "ESD Ends ? Global Associates Begins ?." ESD was a joint partner with the NCUSCR in the Ussuri Project.
  - Ussuri Project: Global Associates in Sustainable Development, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 152)
    Organization formed by George D. Davis.
  - Ussuri Project: Ecologically Sustainable Development Inc. (ESD) Quarterly Reports, 1993-1997 (Box 16, Folder 153)
    Reports to funders.
  - Ussuri Project: Financial Reports, 1994-1997 (Box 16, Folder 154)
  - Ussuri Project: Budgets and Fundraising, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 155)
  - Usuri Project: Fundraising (General A - Z), 1995 (Box 16, Folder 156)
    Gilman Foundation, Liz Claiborne and Art Ortenberg Foundation, Ruth Mott Fund, National Fish and Wildlife Foundation
  - Usuri Project: Funding - Asia Foundation, 1994, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 157)
  - Usuri Project: Funding - Eurasia Foundation, 1993-1995, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 158)
  - Usuri Project: Funding - Freeman Foundation, 1994-1995 (Box 16, Folder 159)
  - Usuri Project: Funding - MacArthur Foundation, 1992-1997 (Box 16, Folder 160)
  - Usuri Project: Funding - Rockefeller Brothers Fund, 1993-1997 (Box 16, Folder 161)
  - Usuri Project: Funding - Trust for Mutual Understanding, 1993-1998 (Box 16, Folder 162)
  - Ussuri Project: Background Materials for U. S. Participants, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 163)
    "Ussuri Watershed Project: Background Materials" packet prepared by the NCUSCR.
  - Ussuri Project: Phase 2 Team Members (May-June 1993), 1993-1996 (Box 17, Folder 164)
    Includes several passport photos.
  - Ussuri Project: American Team Members (A-K), 1993-1997 (Box 17, Folder 165)
    Caroline Alves, Roger Beck, Anita Davis, George Davis, G. Gordon Davis, James C. Dawson, David Hoch, Elizabeth Knup.
  - Ussuri Project: American Team Members (L-Z), 1993-1996 (Box 17, Folder 166)
    Bruce G. Marcot, Arthur D. Pedersen, Philip T. Siarkowski, Charles Slaughter (1 item), Zane Smith, Gerald Stryker.
  - Ussuri Project: Wingspread Conference Background Materials, 1994 February 25-27 (Box 17, Folder 167)
    Conference on Promoting Sustainable Economic Development and Biodiversity in the Amur/Ussuri Watershed. See also conference files in RG 1 (FA772), box 142.
  - Ussuri Project Background and Reference: Environmental Groups in DC and New York City, 1995-1996, undated (Box 17, Folder 168)
  - Ussuri Project Background and Reference: Environmental Organizations and NGOs in China (General), 1993-1997 (Box 17, Folder 169-170)
    Includes correspondence concerning environmental education program.
  - Ussuri Project Background and Reference: Chinese Environmental Organizations (A-Z), 1996-1998 (Box 17, Folder 171)
  - Ussuri Project Background and Reference: Beijing Environment and Development Institute (Ma Zhong), 1992-1995 (Box 17, Folder 172)
  - Ussuri Project Background and Reference: Hong Kong Environmental Organizations, 1994, 1996-1997 (Box 17, Folder 173)
    Includes 1994 discussion of Mai Po wetlands.
  - Ussuri Project Background and Reference: Nature Reserves in China, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 174)
  - Ussuri Project Background and Reference: Econet Conferences and Background Materials, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 175)
  - Ussuri Project Background and Reference: Council on Foreign Relations, China and the Environment Series, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 176)
    Correspondence, papers, and background readings.
  - Ussuri Project Background and Reference: Environment (General), 1990-1994 (Box 18, Folder 177)
    Correspondence, conferences, background readings and clippings. Also includes materials on Environmental Fundraising, Pandas, Tumen River Delta, and U. S. Environmental Resources (websites).
  - Ussuri Project Background and Reference: Siberia and Russian Far East, 1991-1993 (Box 18, Folder 178)
  - Ussuri Project Background and Reference: Siberia - Environment, 1992-1993 (Box 18, Folder 179)
  - Ussuri Project Background and Reference: Regional Environment - Northeast China and Russia, 1992-1993 (Box 18, Folder 180)
    Trade and Cooperation, Geography and Land Use, Ecology
  - Ussuri Project Background and Reference: Elizabeth Luce Moore Leadership Program for Chinese Women (Elizabeth Knup file), 1995-1996 (Box 18, Folder 181)
    Program of the Institute for International Education. The topic for 1995-1996 was "Women in the Environment and Community." Knup served on the program's Advisory Committee. The file consists mainly of applications for the 1996 program.
  - Curriculum Development, 1965-1969 (Box 27, Folder 268-270)
  - Curriculum Projects: General (Correspondence), 1970-1971 (Box 27, Folder 271)
  - Curriculum Projects: General (Supplementary Material), 1962-1970 (Box 27, Folder 272)
  - Harvard Curriculum Project, World Affairs Council of Boston, 1968-1971 (Box 27, Folder 273)
    Harvard Field Staff pilot curriculum project, administered by the World Affairs Council. Summer 1969 workshop, and planning for 1970 program.
  - Boston Project (World Affairs Council of Boston), 1970-1971 (Box 27, Folder 274)
    Teachers Information Center workshops on China. Sarah Benet, director.
  - Curriculum Projects: Education Development Corporation (Ezra Vogel), 1971-1972 (Box 27, Folder 275)
  - University of Michigan, Task Force Project on Asian Studies in Education (Report), 1971 August (Box 27, Folder 276)
  - Requests for Information, 1968-1971 (Box 27, Folder 277)
    Requests from educators and others for teaching materials, references, film footage, etc. Includes requests for the National Committee's Critical Guide to Curriculum Units on China, 1968.
  - Requests for Information, 1971-1976 (Box 28, Folder 278-280)
  - Susan Rifkin, Instructional Television Series on China, 1966, 1968 - 1970 September (Box 28, Folder 281-282)
    Also includes correspondence and materials relating to Association for Asian Studies projects and conferences.
  - Association for Asian Studies and Ohio State University, Conference on Asian Studies and Secondary Education, 1970 September - 1971 (Box 28, Folder 283)
    Materials were originally filed as a continuation of the Susan Rifkin, Instructional Television Series on China file.
  - Survey on Status of China Studies in Secondary Schools, 1969-1970 (Box 28, Folder 284)
    Correspondence concerning follow-up proposal to create a clearinghouse for teaching materials on China. For survey report, see folder on China Resource and Curriculum Guide: Resources (Louise Bennett).
  - Directory of Asian Studies in Secondary Education, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 285)
    Edited by Ronald Suleski. Correspondence.
  - Association for Asian Studies, 1969-1976 (Box 28, Folder 286-287)
    Correspondence concerning conferences, programs and annual reports.
  - Center for War/Peace Studies China Questionnaire, 1973 (Box 29, Folder 288)
    Questionnaires on student perceptions of China.
  - New York State, 1968-1973 (Box 29, Folder 289)
    Survey and reports on International Education in New York State.
  - New York State China Trip, 1973-1974 (Box 29, Folder 290)
    Itinerary and notes from the visit of the first New York State Study Group on Modern China in July 1973, and participant list for planned visit of a second Study Group in 1974. File also includes bibliography and list of slides.
  - China Conversations: Tape Requests, 1973-1977 (Box 29, Folder 291-292)
    Includes some comments on series.
  - China Conversations: Study Guides, 1972-1975 (Box 29, Folder 293)
  - Broadcasting Foundation of America, 1973-1977 (Box 29, Folder 294)
    The Broadcasting Foundation of America was the distributor for the China Conversations series.
  - Audiovisual Resources: General, 1970-1972 (Box 29, Folder 295)
    Available Film Footage - Not Marketed (Alessandro Casella reporting for NBC News), 1972, Requests for information on stock footage, 1971-1972, Associated Press filmstrips, 1970, Requests for films (rental of China: Roots of Madness and Red China Diary), 1970, Tapes (for Resource and Curriculum Guide), undated.
  - Audiovisual Materials (mainly since 1975), 1973, 1975-1976 (Box 29, Folder 296-297)
  - Tom Davenport Films, 1970-1973 (Box 30, Folder 298)
  - The Advocates (Television Program), 1970-1971 (Box 30, Folder 299)
    Includes transcript.
  - ABC Scope, "China Briefing" Program, 1967 July 23 (Box 30, Folder 300)
    Television program entitled "China Briefing," moderated by John Scalli and featuring the Harvard Journalists' Seminar.
  - Chelsea House China Film, 1967-1970 (Box 30, Folder 301)
    Mao China Revolution (with Doak Barnett) and other films.
  - Joe De Cola, Dixie Mission Film, 1971-1972 (Box 30, Folder 302)
  - Seven Hundred Million (CBC), 1967-1969 (Box 30, Folder 303)
  - R.C. Hunt, 1970-1971 (Box 30, Folder 304)
    Proposed film on the Cultural Revolution and interest in speaking engagement.
  - Edward LeFevour, China Today (KRON-TV, San Francisco), 1970 (Box 30, Folder 305)
  - China Resource and Curriculum Guide: Edwin Reischauer Introduction, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 306)
    File also includes lists of books on China for high-school students.
  - China Resource and Curriculum Guide: Edward Friedman Essay, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 307)
  - China Resource and Curriculum Guide: Jonathan Spence Essay, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 308)
  - China Resource and Curriculum Guide: Resources (Louise Bennett), 1971 (Box 30, Folder 309)
    File also includes a report on the NCUSCR's 1969 "Survey on Teaching about China in U. S. Secondary Schools".
  - China Resource and Curriculum Guide: Updates (Books), 1972-1974 (Box 30, Folder 310-311)
  - China Resource and Curriculum Guide: Books for High School (since January 1975), 1975-1976 (Box 30, Folder 312)
  - China Resource and Curriculum Guide: Books for High School (since January 1975), 1975-1976 (Box 31, Folder 313)
  - China Resource and Curriculum Guide: Updates (Curriculum Units and Materials), 1972-1973 (Box 31, Folder 314)
  - China Resource and Curriculum Guide: Updates (Resources Section), 1972-1974 (Box 31, Folder 315-316)
  - Educational Leaders, Organizations, and Editors, 1970, undated (Box 31, Folder 317)
    Lists and addresses.
  - European Visual and Aural Materials on China (K. L. Pratt), 1973-1974 (Box 31, Folder 318)
    China: An Index to European Visual and Aural Materials, ed. K. L. Pratt and D. W. S. Gray. Correspondence file.
  - Holt Rinehart and Winston, Inc., Textbook Chapters on China, 1974 (Box 31, Folder 319)
  - Change Magazine, 1974-1975 (Box 31, Folder 320)
  - China Trade Study: Dana Robinson, 1966-1968, 1972 (Box 40, Folder 400-402)
    In December 1966, the Ford Foundation engaged Dana Robinson as a consultant on U. S. and Free World Trade.
  - China Trade Study: Dana Robinson (Papers), 1967-1968 (Box 40, Folder 403)
    "Possible Relationships between Economic and Political Factors in Considering U. S. Policy towards the China Question in the United Nations," 1967 March 18, "An Estimate of the Possible Nature and Extent of Trade between the U. S. and Communist China," 1968 February 6, "The Direction of Communist China's 1967 Foreign Trade and an Estimate of the Possible Nature and Extent of Trade between the U. S. and Communist China," 1968 February 20.
  - Sjeklocha, Paul, 1970-1971 (Box 40, Folder 404)
    Correspondence concerning proposed East-West Trade Mission, which Sjeklocha was organizing on the part of his Inter-Globe Associates, Ltd.
  - China's Economy and Trade, 1968 (Box 40, Folder 405)
    NCUSCR Issues Series, volume 1, number 1.
  - China Trade Study: General, 1968-1970 (Box 40, Folder 406-407)
    Includes Budget and Finance.
  - China Trade Study: Contact Lists, 1967-1969 (Box 40, Folder 408)
    Correspondence and lists from the NCUSCR's National Convocation and other events.
  - China Trade Study: Correspondence with Contributors (Legal and Economic Aspects of China Trade), 1968-1970 (Box 40, Folder 409)
  - China Trade Study Group: Panel 1, 1968-1970 (Box 41, Folder 410)
  - China Trade Study Group: Panel 2, 1969-1970 (Box 41, Folder 411)
  - China Trade Study Group: First Meeting, 1970 January 27 (Box 41, Folder 412)
  - China Trade Study Group: Second Meeting, 1970 March 4 (Box 41, Folder 413)
  - China Trade Study: Report Distribution (Non-Press Requests), 1970 (Box 41, Folder 414)
    China Trade Prospects and U. S. Policy
  - China Trade Study: Press Releases and News Briefing, 1970 February - April (Box 41, Folder 415)
  - China Trade Study: Press Contacts and Coverage, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 416)
  - China Trade Study: Corporation Meetings: General, 1970 April 20-23 (Box 41, Folder 417)
    Corporate Briefing and release of report on U. S. - China Trade. San Francisco and New York.
  - China Trade Study: Corporation Meetings: Program, Brochure, and Invitation Letter, 1970 April 20-23 (Box 41, Folder 418)
  - China Trade Study: Corporation Meetings: San Francisco, Chicago, New York, 1970 April 20-23 (Box 41, Folder 419)
    The Chicago Meeting, scheduled for April 22, was cancelled.
  - China Trade Study: Corporation Meetings: Speakers, 1970 April 20-23 (Box 42, Folder 420-421)
  - China Trade Study: Corporation Meetings: Sponsors and Participants, 1970 April 20-23 (Box 42, Folder 422)
  - China Trade Study: Corporation Meetings: Contributions, 1970 April 20-23 (Box 42, Folder 423)
  - China Trade Study: Corporation Meetings: Invitations, 1970 April 20-23 (Box 42, Folder 424-425)
    Lists (Fortune 500 Companies and others, Top 500 Utilities and Retail) and Follow-Up.
  - Corporation Meetings: Acceptances and Correspondence (San Francisco and New York), 1970 April 20-23 (Box 42, Folder 426-427)
  - China Trade Study: Corporation Meetings: Regrets (A-L), 1970 April 20-23 (Box 42, Folder 428)
  - China Trade Study: Corporation Meetings: Regrets (M-Z), 1970 April 20-23 (Box 43, Folder 429)
  - China Trade Study: John R. Garson, 1969 December 1 (Box 43, Folder 430)
    The American Trade Embargo of China.
  - China Trade Study: Robert F. Dernberger, 1970 February (Box 43, Folder 431)
    The China Trade: What's in It for US? An investigation fo the economic consequences of liberalizing the United States' restrictions on trade with China.
  - China Trade Study: Book Publication and Publicity, 1969-1972 (Box 43, Folder 432-434)
    China Trade Prospects and U. S. Policy (Praeger, 1970). Correspondence with publishers, promotion, and reviews.
  - China Trade Study: Book Requests (Asia Letter Offer), 1970 (Box 43, Folder 435)
  - University Field Staff Program: Harvard Field Staff (Formation), 1966 August-October (Box 45, Folder 451)
- Development, 1964-2007; 10
  The Development series in RG 5 notably includes a set of Foundation Correspondence files. In many cases, these Foundation files include grant applications, proposals, and reports, along with more routine correspondence or funding requests. Other materials include financial reporting and background literature. The series also includes a few individual alphabetical files, from an otherwise unidentified run of general correspondence, and more recent acknowledgements of contributions.
  - General Correspondence: Abramowitz, Sheppie, 1967, 1969 (Box 46, Folder 452)
  - General Correspondence: M, 1965-1968 (Box 46, Folder 453)
    Organizational correspondence (membership and program development).
  - General Correspondence: Robinson, Dana, 1967-1968 (Box 46, Folder 454)
  - General Correspondence: S, 1965-1968 (Box 46, Folder 455-456)
  - General Correspondence: T, 1964-1968 (Box 46, Folder 457)
  - Foundation Correspondence: General, 1968-1970 (Box 46, Folder 458)
  - Foundation Correspondence: General, 1971-1987, 1998 (Box 46, Folder 459)
    Includes 1998 email concerning Starr Foundation.
  - Albert Kunstadter Family Foundation, 1986, 1993-1994 (Box 46, Folder 460)
  - C. E. and S. Foundation, 1999-2003 (Box 46, Folder 461)
  - Carnegie Corporation of New York, 1977-1984 (Box 46, Folder 462)
  - Coca-Cola Foundation, 1986, 2004 (Box 46, Folder 463)
  - Dragon Foundation, 2001-2002 (Box 47, Folder 464)
  - Dragon Foundation, 2001; Digital Media: CD (Box 47, Folder 464)
    CD on the Dragon Foundation, enclosed with brochure and form letter, 2001 November 16.
  - Ford Foundation: Correspondence, 1967-1992 (Box 47, Folder 465-471)
  - Ford Foundation: Correspondence, 1993-2003 (Box 48, Folder 472)
  - Ford Foundation: Grant Payments, 1967-1970 (Box 48, Folder 473)
    Includes 1970 legal caution concerning programs aimed at legislators.
  - Ford Foundation: Literature, 1990-2002 (Box 48, Folder 474)
  - Ford Foundation: Survey of Programs on United States - China Relations and Security Issues, 2001-2003 (Box 48, Folder 475)
    Report and Appendices, 2003 January 8. Survey conducted
  - Freeman Foundation, 1997 (Box 48, Folder 476)
  - Henry Luce Foundation, 1967-2004 (Box 48, Folder 477-479)
  - Henry Luce Foundation (Literature), 1980-2001 (Box 48, Folder 480)
    Includes directories of Luce Scholars, 1980-1982, and sixtieth anniversary history of the Luce Foundation.
  - JDR 3rd Fund, 1967-1975 (Box 49, Folder 481)
  - Johnson Foundation, 1978-1998 (Box 49, Folder 482)
    Includes correspondence and program for Wingspread Conference on "Chinese and American Women: Issues of Mutual Concern," 1979 May 28-29.
  - Lilly Endowment, 1973-1977, 1983 (Box 49, Folder 483)
  - Lingnan Foundation, 2001 (Box 49, Folder 484)
  - LWH Family Foundation, 1999 (Box 49, Folder 485)
    Loren W. Hershey.
  - John D. and Catherine T. MacArthur Foundation, 1995-2003 (Box 49, Folder 486)
  - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA), 1972-1976 (Box 49, Folder 487)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities (NEH), 1970-1974 (Box 49, Folder 488-490)
    University Field Staff and Educational Resources Project.
  - National Endowment for the Humanities (NEH) (Reports), 1975-1976 (Box 50, Folder 491-492)
    Interim progress report for University Field Staffs and Audiotape Program, 1974 September - 1975 July (including progress reports and materials for each of the field staffs), and Final Report for the University Field Staffs and Educational Resources Project, for the 1973-1975 grant period, 1976 April.
  - National Endowment for the Humanities (NEH) (Grant Accounting), 1971-1976 (Box 50, Folder 493-495)
    Field Staffs and Educational Resources grants, also includes some reports for BAYCEP.
  - National Endowment for the Humanities (NEH) (Bay Area China Education Project), 1972-1975 (Box 50, Folder 496)